[
  {
    "question": "Stephen Curry and what fellow NBA three-point specialist are known as the “Splash Brothers”?",
    "choice1": "Draymond Green",
    "choice2": "Seth Curry",
    "choice3": "Klay Thompson",
    "choice4": "Andre Iguodala",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team drafted shooting guard Klay Thompson in the 2011 NBA Draft?",
    "choice1": "Golden State Warriors",
    "choice2": "Dallas Mavericks",
    "choice3": "Memphis Grizzlies",
    "choice4": "Miami Heat",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2011-12 Kawhi Leonard was selected with which overall pick?",
    "choice1": "2nd",
    "choice2": "7th",
    "choice3": "15th",
    "choice4": "17th",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In which team did Arvydas Sabonis play before he went to play in the NBA?",
    "choice1": "Efes Pilsen",
    "choice2": "Olympiakos",
    "choice3": "Panathinaikos",
    "choice4": "Real Madrid",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "In what year did CSKA Moscow win their first Euroleague title?",
    "choice1": "1961",
    "choice2": "1970",
    "choice3": "1965",
    "choice4": "1963",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which European team did Toni Kukoc play for in 1991-1993 before his NBA career began?",
    "choice1": "Union Olimpija",
    "choice2": "Koiarkaaiki Klub Split",
    "choice3": "Alba Berlin",
    "choice4": "Benetton Treviso",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Whose streak of 158 consecutive Euroleague appearances came to an end on October, 2008?",
    "choice1": "J.R. Holden's",
    "choice2": "Derrick Sharp's",
    "choice3": "D'or Fischer's",
    "choice4": "Tal Burstein's",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Philadelphia 76ers center Joel Embiid is a native of which African country?",
    "choice1": "Nigeria",
    "choice2": "Cameroon",
    "choice3": "Senegal",
    "choice4": "Ghana",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first NBA rookie since Allen Iverson to have two consecutive games scoring at least 35 points?",
    "choice1": "Giannis Antetokounmpo",
    "choice2": "James Harden",
    "choice3": "Stephen Curry",
    "choice4": "Trae Young",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Champion NBA point guard Kyrie Irving was born in which country?",
    "choice1": "New Zealand",
    "choice2": "United States",
    "choice3": "Australia",
    "choice4": "United Kingdom",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "NBA brothers Pau and Marc Gasol hail from which foreign country?",
    "choice1": "Greece",
    "choice2": "Germany",
    "choice3": "Spain",
    "choice4": "Bulgaria",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What were the Philadelphia 76ers originally named?",
    "choice1": "Syracuse Nationals",
    "choice2": "Philadelphia Knights",
    "choice3": "Pennsylvania 76ers",
    "choice4": "Pennsylvania Ballers",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What were the Oklahoma City Thunder originally named?",
    "choice1": "Seattle Nationals",
    "choice2": "Oklahoma Royals",
    "choice3": "Buffalo Braves",
    "choice4": "Seattle SuperSonics",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "What were the Washington Wizards originally named?",
    "choice1": "D.C Kings",
    "choice2": "Washington Bullets",
    "choice3": "Baltimore Bullets",
    "choice4": "Washington Mages",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "In 2015, which NBA player broke the record for most points scored in a quarter?(37-point quarter)",
    "choice1": "Klay Thompson",
    "choice2": "LeBron James",
    "choice3": "James Harden",
    "choice4": "Kawhi Leonard",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "In 1999, the Chicago Bulls traded established superstar Scottie Pippen to which other team?",
    "choice1": "Utah Jazz",
    "choice2": "Atlanta Hawks",
    "choice3": "Detroit Pistons",
    "choice4": "Houston Rockets",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following set a records for most free throws made in a game?",
    "choice1": "John Stockton",
    "choice2": "Michael Jordan",
    "choice3": "Dan Majerle",
    "choice4": "Wilt Chamberlain",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Only three players other than Michael Jordan led the league in scoring in the 90s. Which of these was not one of them?",
    "choice1": "Shaquille O'Neal",
    "choice2": "Hakeem Olajuwon",
    "choice3": "David Robinson",
    "choice4": "Allen Iverson",
    "answer": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following NBA retired players,had the most career steals?",
    "choice1": "Larry Bird",
    "choice2": "Karl Malone",
    "choice3": "Julius Erving",
    "choice4": "Scottie Pippen",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which basketball team has the most NBA championships?",
    "choice1": "Chicago Bulls",
    "choice2": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "choice3": "Boston Celtics",
    "choice4": "Golden State Warriors",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the record for most consecutive NBA titles?",
    "choice1": "4",
    "choice2": "5",
    "choice3": "7",
    "choice4": "8",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team won the NBA Championship in 2004?",
    "choice1": "Detroit Pistons",
    "choice2": "Los Angeles Lakers",
    "choice3": "Miami Heat",
    "choice4": "Sacramento Kings",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What country is Luka doncic from?",
    "choice1": "Latvia",
    "choice2": "Lithuania",
    "choice3": "Slovakia",
    "choice4": "Slovenia",
    "answer": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which basketball team has the most Israeli basketball premier league championships?",
    "choice1": "Maccabi Tel Aviv",
    "choice2": "Hapoel Jerusalem",
    "choice3": "Hapoel Holon",
    "choice4": "Hapoel Tel Aviv",
    "answer": 1
  }
]
